Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 5: Dishware, 1801-2010; 102 boxes; 12 items
  - Ceramic mug, 1957; 1 box (Box A.18)
    Black. "Freshman Prom 1957."
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.14)
    Seal, "Thomas B Hamilton"
    E4825
    Gift of the Nassau Club
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.19)
    White, with University seal.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.17)
    "NBA 'We did our part'". Frank T. Buchner '34. Fundraiser?
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.19)
    EX5003
    Green with gold University seal.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.17)
    Orange with seal.
    Gift of Sackett M Dickinson '05
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.17)
    White, orange and black with seal, tiger and pennants.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.15)
    Football shaped with University seal.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.24)
    Black and orange with metal rim.
    Gift of Cyril I Nelson '48
  - Ceramic mug, 1948; 1 box (Box A.38)
    Off-white with orange and black, "Princeton 1923-1948" with "23" encircled in center.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.38)
    White with seal and "Princeton University," "1936" and "Jac Weller."
    Class of 1936
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.38)
    Orange and black with shield in brown and football player on back.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.37)
    White with "P 27" in orange and black and "Y 2" in blue.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.37)
    AR.1998.025
    Off-white with orange and black and "P 1912."
  - Ceramic mug, 1912; 1 box (Box A.37)
    AR.2000.111
    "P 1902 Decennial Reunion" in black.
    Class of 1902
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.50)
    AR.2008.024
    Princeton Shield. Class of 1951, "Charles Augustus Brothman." Music box in bottom, plays, "Going Back to Nassau Hall."
    Class of 1951
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.51)
    AR.2008.050
    Tiger with Princeton shield, "1909" in orange. Black and green, gold trim, white inside.
  - Ceramic mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.51)
    "P '09." Black with orange letters, gold trim, white inside.
  - Ceramic Mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.46)
    Princeton Shield.
  - Ceramic Urn, Undated; 1 box (Box A.47)
    With Palmer Stadium, Blair Tower, Nassau hall and a roaring tiger.
  - Crystal goblet, Undated; 1 box (Box 5)
    13 inches tall. Handpainted inscriptions.
    AR.2006.051
    Belonged to Allan Marquand, Class of 1874. Given by G. Allan Forsyth, Class of 1953.
  - Egg server?, Undated; 1 box (Box A.26)
    White ceramic with University seal.
  - Espresso cup, Undated; 1 box (Box A.26)
    Ceramic with University seal.
    Gift of Charles Hathaway '23
  - Glass, 1956; 1 box (Box A.23)
    Bicentennial glass with orange U. seal and Nassau Hall.
  - Glass, Undated; 1 box (Box A.23)
    Old U. seal and motto.
  - Glass, 1954 March; 1 box (Box A.23)
    "Princeton in Texas"
  - Glass, 1957; 1 box (Box A.23)
    PAA of Maryland. Dinner and Dance for Dodds.
  - Glass, 1956; 1 box (Box A.23)
    Bicentennial, Class of 1926.
  - Glass, 1990; 1 box (Box 13)
    AR.2004.097
    Class of 1945. 45th reunion glass.
  - Glass, 1954; 1 box (Box 13)
    Class of 1904 50th Reunion glass.
  - Glass, Undated; 1 box (Box 39)
    Princeton shield and motto.
  - Glass, 1967 June 7-11; 1 box (Box 42)
    Class of 1942. 25th reunion. Glass with "42" logo and cartoon tiger.
  - Glass., Undated; 1 box (Box A.23)
    U. seal.
  - Glass shaker, Undated; 1 box (Box A.39)
    with shield.
  - Large tankard, 1899; 1 box (Box A.24)
    Pewter. From the estate of Professor McClure. "From a fair Sinner to the Monks."
    EX4921
    Presented by Mrs. E Dudley Johnson
  - Lowball glass, 1970 June 4; 1 box (Box A.43)
    Class of 1915. 55th reunion.
  - Lowball glass, Undated; 1 box (Box A.44)
  - Mini mug, 1912; 1 box (Box A.5)
    Seal and 1912.
  - Mini mug, 1907; 1 box (Box A.6)
    EX4733
    Tri-handled reunions.
  - Mini mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.7)
    U. seal and "Princeton." White.
  - Mini mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.5)
    U. seal. Green.
  - Mini mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.6)
    Tiger and "Princeton." Orange.
  - Mini mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.5)
    Tiger head. White.
  - Mini mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.7)
    Tiger bust. White.
  - Mini mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.5)
    Tiger bust. Green.
  - Mini mug, 1952; 1 box (Box A.5)
    Tri-handled, with U. seal and tiger bust. Green.
  - Mini mug, 1952; 1 box (Box A.7)
    Princeton Tower Club, "House Parties '52."
  - Mini mug, 1912; 1 box (Box A.7)
    Off-white, with shield and year.
  - Mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.29)
    Orange with football on side, black handle.
  - Mug, 1971; 1 box (Box A.32)
    White with "Cannon Club Princeton University" in green. "James D. Hess."
    Class of 1971
  - Mug, circa 1912; 1 item
    Ceramic. Green with seal and "1912."
  - Mug, circa 1889; 1 item
    Ceramic. Green with tiger head breaking through seal. "89" on back.
  - Mug, circa 1889; 1 item
    Ceramic. Green with stalking tiger and seal. "89" on back.
  - Mug, Undated; 1 box (Box 12)
    AR.2005.091
    Class of 1915. Off-white mug with orange University seal and black edges.
  - Mug, Undated; 1 box (Box 12)
    Class of 1904. Black mug with orange numbers overlapping each other.
  - Mug, 1903; 1 box (Box 12)
    AR.2007.003
    Class of 1893. 10th reunion mug. Off-white with Princeton Shield and two tigers. "Charles H. Angell"
    Class of 1893
  - Mug, Undated; 1 box (Box 13)
    White mug with Princeton Shield and "Princeton" in Gothic print. Picture of three men in colonial garb.
  - Mug, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Teal mug called "Wonder Mug." Black lettering "USS Princeton CG 59" along with picture of ship
  - Mug, 1950; 1 box (Box 32)
    AR.2009.095
    Miniature mug. "1950 House Party. Princeton Prospect Club."
  - Mug, Undated; 1 box (Box 32)
    AR.2011.046
    Class of 1931. Black mug with gold insignia.
  - Mug, 1956; 1 box (Box 32)
    Class of 1936. 20th reunion. Beer stein with Princeton logo. Initials printed "N. H. S."
    AR.2010.137
    Received from Debbie Tillinghast. Possibly originally owned by Newton Hale Shaffer '36?
  - Old spoon, Undated; 1 box (Box A.28)
    AR.1996.040
  - Pewter chalice, Undated; 1 box (Box A.28)
    Presented to "John E Parker, Jr."
    E 4769
    Gift of William J Hazel, received '53.
  - Pewter mug, Undated; 1 box (Box A.22)
  - Pewter mug, 1901; 1 box (Box A.29)
    "To Max Farrand" with U. seal and signatures.
  - Pewter mug, 1912; 1 box (Box A.19)
    "EMB 1912" and signatures.
    AR.1996.022
    Gift of Kenneth Barnhart '45.
  - Pewter mug, 1933; 1 box (Box A.19)
    EX4584 5
    "JBFW 1933 187" and signatures.
    Class of 1933
  - Pewter mug, 1935; 1 box (Box A.21)
    "MCM Jr. 1935 10"
  - Pewter mug, 1899; 1 box (Box A.20)
    EX4588
    "Ned Benson" Ivy Club seal 1899 and signatures.
  - Pewter mug, 1904; 1 box (Box A.20)
    "Lynn M Adsit 1904" Cottage Club seal and signatures.
  - Pewter mug, 1898; 1 box (Box A.22)
    EX4574/1
    "Fred JH Sutton '98" and signatures.
  - Pewter mug, 1943; 1 box (Box A.21)
    "GR Brown 1943 151"
    Class of 1943
  - Pewter mug, 1898; 1 box (Box A.22)
    EX4574/2
    "Billy Pell" 1898 Colonial Club seal and signatures.
  - Pewter mug, 1933; 1 box (Box A.20)
    EX4584
    "JBF Wainwright '33" Wing engraved on mug.
  - Pewter mug, 1904; 1 box (Box A.21)
    "J Nelson Carter 1904" Cap and Gown seal and signatures.
    Gift of J Nelson Carter '04
  - Pewter mug with lid, Undated; 1 box (Box A.50)
    Princeton Shield. "Charles Augustus Brothman."
  - Pitcher, circa 1889; 1 item
    Ceramic. Green with seal, "Princeton" on front, "89" on back.
  - Pitcher, Undated; 1 item
    Ceramic. Green with dragon handle. Tiger lying on seal.
  - Plastic cup, Undated; 1 box (Box A.46)
    Frist Campus Center dining services plastic cup.
  - Plate to soup tureen, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box A.4)
    White with pink roses. Belonged to George Goldie, director of athletics under president McCosh.
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    AR.2010.094
    Class of 1955. 55th reunion. White plastic cup with tiger blowing into horn. "Matt's Premium Beer."
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    Class of 1965. 45th reunion. Orange plastic cup with "Sounds of '65" logo with record and tiger playing guitar.
    Class of 1965
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    Class of 1970. 40th reunion. White plastic cup with 1970 bug logo and Yuengling logo.
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    Class of 2005. 5th reunion. White plastic cup with superhero tiger logo.
    Class of 2005
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    Class of 2000. 10th reunion. White plastic cup with "'00 hangs 10" logo.
    Class of 2000
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    Class of 1995. 15th reunion. White plastic cup with black logo for "Top Tiger"
    Class of 1995
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    Class of 1980. 30th reunion. White plastic cup with "80 @ 30: Together Again" logo.
    Class of 1980
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 31)
    Class of 1975. 35th reunion. White plastic cup with "Millennium Moment" logo.
    Class of 1975
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    AR.2009.023
    Class of 1988. 20th reunion. White plastic cup with "Lasso the 20th!" logo.
    Class of 1988
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    Class of 1973. 35th reunion. White plastic cup with "First Class Memories" logo.
    Class of 1973
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    Class of 1998. 10th reunion. White plastic cup with bowling logo. "Going Back to Bowl Nassau."
    Class of 1998
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    Class of 1983. 25th reunion. White plastic cup with "83 Nation" shield logo.
    Class of 1983
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    Class of 1993. 15th reunion. White plastic cup with "Hawaii One Five-O" logo.
    Class of 1993
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    Class of 2003. 5th reunion. White plastic cup with "What Happens at The Fifth, Stays at the Fifth."
    Class of 2003
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    Class of 1968. 40th reunion. White plastic cup with "Timeless" logo.
    Class of 1968
  - Reunion cup, 2008; 1 box (Box 33)
    White plastic cup with guitar-playing tiger logo.
  - Reunion cup, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. White plastic cup with "Roarin' 25th" logo.
  - Reunion glass, 1976; 1 box (Box A.37)
    AR.2000.023
    "1926 50th Reunion 1976" and mascot.
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 box (Box A.8)
    Short can, white, with tiger leaning on "P."
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 box (Box A.9)
    Tiger with various decade pennants, orange can
  - Reunions beer can, 1967; 1 box (Box A.9)
  - Reunions beer can, 1973; 1 box (Box A.9)
  - Reunions beer can, 1961; 1 box (Box A.9)
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 box (Box A.9)
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 box (Box A.9)
    Tiger lying on a keg.
  - Reunions beer can, 1964; 1 box (Box A.9)
  - Reunions beer can, 1962; 1 box (Box A.9)
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 box (Box A.8)
    Tall with black sticker of white tigers.
  - Reunions beer can, 1962; 1 box (Box A.9)
    Class of 1937
  - Reunions beer can, 1965; 1 box (Box A.8)
    Class of 1940
  - Reunions beer can, 1967; 1 box (Box A.8)
    30th for the class of 1937.
    Ira Dorian
  - Reunions beer can, 1973; 1 box (Box A.8)
    10th for 1963, orange, tiger in space capsule.
    Class of 1963
  - Reunions beer can, 1962 June 7; 1 box (Box A.41)
    AR.2001.062
    Class of 1942. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, Undated; 1 box (Box A.41)
    20th Reunion
  - Reunions beer can, 1971 June 3; 1 box (Box A.41)
    Class of 1951. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1968 June; 1 box (Box A.41)
    Class of 1943. 25th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1970 June; 1 box (Box A.41)
    Class of 1945. 25th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1971 June; 1 box (Box A.41)
    Class of 1941. 30th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, Undated; 1 box (Box A.41)
    "Welcome Princeton Alumni".
  - Reunions beer can, 1972 June 1; 1 box (Box A.41)
    Class of 1952. 20th reunion.
    Class of 1952
  - Reunions beer can, 1969; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1939. 30th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1970 June 5; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1960. 10th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1973; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1953. 20th reunion.
    Class of 1953
  - Reunions beer can, 1968; 1 box (Box A.42)
    1968.
  - Reunions beer can, 1971 June 3; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1946. 25th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1975; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1955. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1990; 1 box (Box A.46)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. Tiger catching a cicada.
  - Reunions plastic cup, Undated; 1 box (Box A.42)
    30th reunion. "It's about time" and a drunk tiger on top of an hour glass
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1988 June 2; 1 box (Box A.42)
    "Reunions June 2-4 1988" and a drunk tiger on top of an hourglass
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1989 June 1; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1939. 50th reunion.
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1989 June 1; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1969. 20th reunion.
    Class of 1969
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1992 June 4; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1972. 20th reunion.
    Class of 1972
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1988 June 2; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1983. 5th reunion.
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1990 June 7; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions plastic cup, Undated; 1 box (Box A.42)
    Leaping tiger and "Princeton Reunions" on front.
  - Reunions plastic cup, 2000 May 25; 1 box (Box A.46)
    Class of 1970. 30th reunion. Cicada pattern and "Return of the Weevil Empire" on front. One duplicate.
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1995 May 25; 1 box (Box A.46)
    Class of 1970. 25th reunion. Cicada pattern with "In Locusts Parentis Non Compos Mantis" on front.
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1990 June 7; 1 box (Box A.46)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. Cicada pattern.
  - Scotch bottle, 1963; 1 box (Box A.13)
    Bottled for reunions. "Touchdown Club"
  - Sherry glass, Undated; 1 box (Box A.43)
  - Shot glass, Undated; 1 box (Box A.43)
  - Silver bowl, 1968 May 12; 1 box (Box 26)
    AR.2007.018
    Covered by blue cloth. Presented to Walter Nollner by the Princeton University Glee Club
  - Silver spoon, circa 1891-1900; 1 box (Box A.27)
    "Commemorating Frederick Brokaw of the Class of 1892 who died in July 1891 in an attempt to rescue a drowning woman at Elberon, N.J. A portrait and his name appear in the bowl of the spoon. Patent granted to Theodore Combes of Philadelphia.
    October 18, 1892. Given by James D. Zirin '61."
  - Silver spoon, Undated; 1 box (Box A.27)
    Silver spoon with football player and seal on handle.
    Given by William E. Bardusch, Jr. '39.
  - Small cup, Undated; 1 box (Box A.6)
    U. seal. White with gold trim set on square base.
  - Small plate, Undated; 1 box (Box A.2)
    AR.1997.079
    Nassau Hall in center with border of red roses.
  - Small silver spoon, circa 1864; 1 box (Box A.27)
    Note attached. "Old small spoon used by Samuel Miller Gardner through his days at Princeton College.. ."
    Made by Daniel Hedgers a silver smith of East Hampton, Long Island.
  - Small wine bottle, 1974; 1 box (Box A.14)
    Bottled for reunions. "Viniio do Tigre"
    Class of 1944
  - Soup tureen, circa 1801-1900; 1 box (Box A.3)
    Ceramic. Pink rose pattern on white.
    Belonged to George Goldie, director of athletics under president McCosh. Gift of John A. Bryan (brother of Goldie's son in law), Feb 14, 1968. Letter attached.
  - Sterling silver spoon, Undated; 1 box (Box A.27)
    AR.2008.042
    University seal and black inlay design on handle.
  - Sugar basket, 1855; 1 box (Box A.28)
    Metal
    EX4258
    Recovered from Nassau Hall fire of 1855. Presented by W.H. Lyrie, class of 1890.
  - Tri-handled Reunion Cup, 1887; 1 item
    Class of 1877's 10th reunion. White with tigers, part of song "Old Nassau."
  - Water bottle, 2001 September 28; 1 box (Box A.44)
    From the Installation of Shirley M. Tilghman, 10th president of Princeton University.
  - Water bottle, Undated; 1 box (Box A.46)
    Frist Campus Center water bottle.
  - Water bottle, 2010; 1 box (Box 38)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Orange bottle with black top and "Roarin' 25th" logo.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates, 1930; 1 box (Box A.1)
    EX4956 /2
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china. Complete set in original packaging.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates, Undated; 1 box (Box A.2)
    Cream colored gold trim. Various campus views. Complete set. #41 of 100 sets made.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates, 1930; 1 box (Box A.1c)
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china. Duplicates of box A-1 and box 30.
    Gift of Mrs. Frank S. Hoag, Jr. in memory of Frank S. Hoag, Jr. '31.Response letter enclosed.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates, 1930; 1 box (Box A.49)
    AR.2007.123
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates, 1930; 1 box (Box 30)
    EX4956 /1
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china. Near-complete set in original packaging. Duplicates of box A-1.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates., 1930; 1 box (Box A.48)
    AR.2002.070
  - Whiskey bottle, 1963; 1 box (Box 4)
    AR.2004.063
    Class of 1923. 40th reunion bottle of Kentucky bourbon whiskey.
  - Whiskey bottle, 1977; 1 box (Box 4)
    Class of 1927. 50th reunion bourbon whiskey bottle.
  - Whisky nip bottle, 1963; 1 box (Box A.21)
    Bottled for reunions. "Old Forester"
  - White plate, 1941; 1 box (Box A.2)
    Wedgwood. Class of 1911 seal with affixed description. Designed for 30th reunion by Curtis Fields.
- Series 6: Embossers, 1866-1912; 4 boxes
  This series contains Princeton embossers.
  - Embosser, Undated; 1 box (Box E.4)
    1". U Seal w/"BIBL UNIV PRINCETON" around it.
  - Embosser, 1866; 1 box (Box E.4)
    2". "The Trustees of the Students' Aid Organization. Incorporated 1866 New Jersey."
  - Embosser, Undated; 1 box (Box E.3)
    3". U Seal. "SIGILLUM UNIVERSITATIS PRINCETONIENSIS"
  - Embosser, Undated; 1 box (Box E.4)
    "University Library Princeton, NJ."
  - Embosser, 1912; 1 box (Box E.4)
    "Society of the Claw Princeton University." "Founded Jan. 13.A.D.1912 By the Class of 1894."
- Series 7: Grounds and Buildings, 1701-1982; 12 boxes; 2 items
  The grounds and building memorabilia contains pieces of buildings, keys, and bells.
  - Banister piece, Undated; 1 box (Box B.5)
    from Reunion Hall that once supported hand of John F. Kennedy.
  - Bell, 1926; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Gillett and Johnston - London 1926. Large.
  - Bell, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    No markings. Medium sized.
  - Bell, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Small "68" painted on it.
  - Bell, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Small. Excess mold metal still attached.
  - Bell, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Small with handle. "12" stamped in handle.
  - Bell clapper, circa 1890; 1 box (Box D.1)
    EX4475
    Dark and iron. Watch charm from clapper of Old North taken by class of 1894 men (G. H. Bright, L. I. Reichner) in freshman year.
  - Bell clapper, circa 1910; 1 box (Box E.3)
    "10" inscribed on side.
  - Bell clapper, circa 1950; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Mounted on wood. Class of 1950. Black clapper with orange lettering. "Nassau Hall."
    Class of 1950
    AR.2006.001
    Given by R. Kenneth Perry '50.
  - Bell clapper, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Mounted on wood. Orange wooden mount. Rust-colored clapper.
  - Bell mold, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    AR.1994.009
    Large, yellow.
  - Bell mold, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Medium.
  - Bronze key, 1931; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Bronze key to Nassau Hall. Used for ceremonies in June 1931.
  - Bronze key in wooden box., 1978; 1 box (Box D.3 (2/20/12/3))
    Box has seal on top. Nassau Hall Ceremonial Key. Letter enclosed from Frederick Fox.
    letter "as discussed. I think J Douglas Brown '19 gave this to me, saying it was made for Bicentennial gifts."
  - Cross section of railroad tie, 1855; 1 box (Box D.3)
    imprinted w/250, tie originally removed from Nassau Hall. Also stamped with 1855.
    AR.1996.096
    Gift of Renato R Carazzai
  - Fireplace bricks from Osborn Clubhouse, 1891-1892; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    Wedge-shaped yellow Roman bricks from fireplace arch in Trophy Room, Osborn Clubhouse (built 1891-1892), magnesium iron-spot type bricks, made by Sayre-Fisher Brick Company, N.J.
    AR.2011.099
    Gift of W. Barksdale Maynard '88
  - Football Goal Post, 1938 November 12; 1 box (Box D.5)
    Piece. Sat Nov 12, 1938. P-20, Y-7.
  - Football Goal Post, Undated; 1 box (Box D.5)
    Piece. Signatures along gray portion.
  - Football goal post piece, 1946 November 2; 1 box (Box D.5)
    from November 2, 1946 Princeton-Penn game.
  - Iron #2, 1926; 1 item
    "John C. Green School of Engineering 1926" written on back.
  - Key, Undated; 1 box (Box D.3)
    EX4463
    Honorary key to Firestone Library.
  - Metal pin, Undated; 1 box (Box D-)
    "Princeton University 334 Campus Privilege." letter enclosed.
    letter "... Presumably, the Department of Grounds and Buildings issued these passes to vendors coming onto campus in years past."
  - Sign, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    "Class of 1889 Library of American History"
  - Sign, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    "Class of 1883 Library of Political Science and Jurisprudence"
  - Sign, Undated; 1 box (Box D-Open (under stairs))
    AR.1993.017
    "The Daily Princetonian - Business Dep't."
  - Silver key, 1932; 1 box (Box D.3)
    EE.03/7/80
    Silver "Key to University Chapel turned over to me by Pres. Hibben June 1932, VLC. "S. Yellin" inscribed on top.
  - Small bell clapper, Undated; 1 box (Box D.1)
    Dark and iron. Watch fob?
    EX4359
    Henry E. Hale (1892)
  - Small bell clapper, Undated; 1 box (Box D.1)
    Dark and iron. 2.5" long
  - Small bell clapper., Undated; 1 box (Box D.1)
    Watch Fob? Silvery. Clapper made from Nassau Hall bell.
    EX4117
    C. D. Hart (1892)
  - Small fragment of bell, 1855; 1 box (Box D.1)
    Dark and iron. Nassau Hall bell fragment from the fire of 1855.
    EX4255
    Rev. Peters (1870)
  - Small fragment of bell, 1803; 1 box (Box D.1)
    Dark and iron. Nassau Hall bell fragment from the fire of 1803.
    EX4491
    W. Robertson
  - Splinter from goalpost, 1938 November 12; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Princeton 20 -Yale 7, Sat Nov 12, 1938.
  - Structural, Undated; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Brick swirl from Marquand Chapel. Painted brown.
  - Structural, circa 1725; 1 box (Box D.1)
    EX4892
    Wood piece; "Fragment of the log building known as Log College 1725" on the plaque attached; "40 Mercer Street Princeton, NJ Elmer Adler" written in black.
  - Structural, Undated; 1 box (Box D.4)
    Metal flower from Capital in Chancellor Green student center.
  - Structural, circa 1881-1890; 1 box (Box D.4)
    Concrete swirl. Possibly from old Marquand building.
    Mr. Wainwright brought to archives from Halsey Thomas' office. Note attached.
  - Structural, 1982; 1 box (Box D.4)
    Stone from Nassau hall. From insertion of 1982 class stone in South face of building.
    Note attached.
  - Structural, 1982; 1 box (Box D.4)
    Brick from steps of Clio hall. Taken from renovations in 1982.
  - Structural, 1877; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Banister cap from Witherspoon hall.
  - Structural, 1899; 1 box (Box D.3)
    Piece of old Bulletin Elm-- used by Dr. Miremay? And given to Mrs. Miramay on their fifth anniversary 1899.
    Note glued on back, hard to read.
  - Structural, 1944; 1 box (Box D.3)